{
    "subject": "resource/The_Drowsy_Chaperone",
    "predicate": "property/awards",
    "object": "Drama Desk Outstanding Musical",
    "human_readable": "The Drowsy Chaperone won a Drama Desk Award for Outstanding Musical.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9266970157623291,
            "question": "For what category did The Drowsy Chaperone receive the Drama Desk Award?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9000595211982727,
            "question": "What does winning a Drama Desk Award signify for a production like The Drowsy Chaperone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8748036026954651,
            "question": "Was The Drowsy Chaperone recognized for a musical performance?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8142338395118713,
            "question": "What award did The Drowsy Chaperone win?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7992530465126038,
            "question": "What is the name of the award that The Drowsy Chaperone won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.773022472858429,
            "question": "Are there other awards that The Drowsy Chaperone might have won?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7637661695480347,
            "question": "Is The Drowsy Chaperone considered an outstanding work in the theater world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.575476348400116,
            "question": "What might be some elements that contributed to The Drowsy Chaperone's success?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4295452833175659,
            "question": "What kind of production is The Drowsy Chaperone?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32349351048469543,
            "question": "Can you think of other musicals that have won similar awards?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The Drowsy Chaperone won a Drama Desk Award for Outstanding Musical.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1116_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What kind of production is The Drowsy Chaperone?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1116_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What might be some elements that contributed to The Drowsy Chaperone's success?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1116_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is The Drowsy Chaperone considered an outstanding work in the theater world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1116_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_13.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1116_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that \"The Drowsy Chaperone\" was chosen best musical of the New York theatre season and won multiple Drama Desk Awards, including Outstanding Musical."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}